GRANT GLOMSTEAD

7050 Hatchery Rd, Waterford MI, 48327 gglomstead@comcast.net (248)-410-9059

Objective

Having recently graduated with a master's degree in engineering technology at Wayne State University, I plan on obtaining a challenging job in the Audio/Visual/Broadcast engineering field that will jump-start a long, successful career. Along with years of experience in the IT field, and a degree focusing on media and technology from Michigan State, I plan to use my wide array of skills to succeed in the AV-tech industry.

Education

Wayne State University Graduated in May 2019.

42 W Warren Ave, Detroit, MI 48202 Master's in Engineering Technology.

Michigan State University Graduated in the summer of 2017.

East Lansing, Michigan 48824 Major: B.S. in Media and Information.

Minor: Information and Technology.

Work Experience

System Support Specialist at Marsh and McLennan Agency 03/2018 – Present

Duties: Imaging computers, managing servers, working in active directory, and general computer maintenance. Supervisor – AJ Michaud: 989-355-0145.

System Administrator/Video Producer at Line2Line Coatings 06/2011 - Present

Duties: Promotional video production, and system administration. Performed system security, server installation, video surveillance and more. Supervisor - Andy Suman: 248-310-1850.

Technician Assistant at CAS Technology Department at MSU 04/2015 – 08/2017

Duties: Installing, maintaining, and fixing a wide array of computers and other technology in the Communication, Arts, Sciences building at Michigan State University, which houses over three thousand audio visual machines. Supervisor – Sam Mills: 517-490-1179.

Internship at DMC Huron Valley Sinai Hospital 05/2012 - 06/2012

Duties: Internship with the Information-Technology Department and other departments such as: Marketing, Operating Room, Cath Lab, Facilities, and more. Supervisor - Deana Brightman.

Skills Summary

- Knowledge and experience with web-based languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and SQL, plus other languages such as C++, PLC, Atmel AVR, and Python.
- Certificate in Fanuc Handling Tool Operations, Robot Programming and ROBOGUIDE Simulation Course.
- Skills dealing with implementation, maintenance, and problem solving on all computer operating systems.
- Experience with video/audio production and graphic design as well as Adobe Creative Suite.
- Hands on experience with Extron, Textron, and other audio and video components while installing and implementing technology in projects such as the new Spartan Newsroom and Immersive Media/Motion Capture Studio at MSU, as well as other locations.
- Feel free to browse my portfolio at: https://glomstea.github.io/